impress.ly 2018-06-24

# 

  This Privacy Policy applies to all users ​before​ May 23, 2018. Beginning on ​May 23, 2018​, our new Privacy
  Policy will apply to all new users and all users in the EU/EEA member countries. The ​new Privacy Policy
  will be effective on ​June 23, 2018​ for users outside the EU/EEA member countries who signed up for
  services before May 23, 2018. The legacy version of the Privacy Policy will remain posted here until July
  23, 2018 for your reference.
                                        PRIVACY AND COOKIE STATEMENT
                                        Last modified on September 3, 2015
The privacy of all of our users and visitors to our website (the “User”) is very important to Impress.ly. This
Privacy and Cookie Statement describes how your Personal Data (as defined below) may be collected,
processed, used and/or disclosed when you use or access a mobile app or mobile site on Impress.ly’s
platform (collectively, the “Service”). “Personal Data” shall mean any data that directly or indirectly
identifies a natural person. This Privacy and Cookie Statement applies to ​www.Impress.ly​ and any and all
subdomains (e.g. my​.impress.ly​). We recommend you read it carefully. Terms that are not defined in this
Privacy and Cookie Statement shall have the meaning set forth in Impress.ly's Terms & Conditions, which
are available at [                   ].
1.​ ​Who is Impress.ly
The Impress.ly website (the “Website”) and Service are operated by AppMachine B.V. doing business as
Impress.ly (“Impress.ly”). AppMachine B.V. is a private company with limited liability in accordance with
Dutch laws, having its registered office at the Abe Lenstra boulevard 44, 8848 JB in Heerenveen. You can
also reach Impress.ly by email at support@Impress.ly.
2.​ ​Type of Personal Data collected and stored by Impress.ly
      A.​ ​Essential Personal Data to create your Account
When you create an Account, you have to provide some Personal Data including your email address and
your full name. You also have the option to provide your phone number. Impress.ly stores the Personal
Data it collects and you provide in connection with your use of the Service.
      B.​ ​Personal Data Collected to use our Service
In order to use our Service, you have to provide additional Personal Data including your billing information.
Any credit card information you provide while using our Service will be processed and handled by
Impress.ly’s payment provider.
As a User, the following information about you will be stored in our databases:
-           your name;
-           your email address;
-           billing address details;
-           if you are a company:
o                    invoice details

o                   company’s address details
-           telephone number
If you decide to become an Impress.ly Reseller the following information will also be stored in our
databases:
-           your company name;
-           your company’s address details;
-           your company invoice details;
-           contact person details (name and email address).
By using the Service you may provide additional Personal Data to Impress.ly and third parties, such as
Personal Data for inclusion in or to be processed by the App. Impress.ly is a processor and not the
controller of such Personal Data.
      C.​ ​Automatically generated information​ ​about users
Like most other websites and online services, Impress.ly gathers and processes automatically generated
information about how you use the Service. The information gathered includes your IP address and/or a
unique device ID. If you publish your App through our Service, such information is also automatically
generated about how users of your App. This information helps us to better understand how our Service is
used, to inform you how your App is used, and how we can improve the Service to suit user needs. If you
enable the user authorization features inside your app, the following additional information will be stored
about your users:
•           Name;
•           Email address;
•           Age range;
•           Gender;
•           Additional profile information returned by an external provider such as Facebook or LinkedIn.
To provide you with information about the usage of your app we also collect the following information on
an anonymized basis (provided, however, that if the user authorization features are enabled we are able to
link the anonymous information to a user once they login):
•           The moment when the user opens up your app;
•           The blocks they've opened inside your app and the amount of time they've spend in this block;
•           Actions such as music playback, opening urls etc.;
•           The moment when the user leaves the app.
3.​ ​For what purposes does Impress.ly process Personal Data?
      A.​ ​Purposes
            Impress.ly processes Personal Data to:
      -     enable you to create and Account and use the Service;
      -     keep you updated with relevant information about the Service;
      -     inform you about other Impress.ly products or services;
      -     improve and/or customize the Service;
      -     to prevent fraud;

       -     provide support;
       -     at your request or if we are required to do so to comply with applicable law as determined in
             Impress.ly’s sole discretion.
       B.​ ​Use of Personal Data by Impress.ly
Impress.ly aims to keep you informed of any changes to its Services. And may use your Personal Data to
notify you of such these changes. Please be aware that you will also receive emails and/or notifications
from Impress.ly concerning the proper functioning of your Account.
When you write to Impress.ly with an enquiry, request or question, you may choose to include some
Personal Data. Such communications and any additional data supplied will be stored by Impress.ly.
Impress.ly may use your email address to reply to you and your Personal Data may also be used to help us
improve or respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs.
       C.​ ​Transmission of Personal Data to third parties
Impress.ly does not sell, trade or rent your Personal Data to third parties without your prior consent.
However, Impress.ly may provide your Personal Data to third parties as required to provide the Service to
you or for carrying out your instructions, such as for making payments.
Impress.ly may provide “aggregated anonymous data” (which is data that cannot be traced back to you) to
third parties regarding the usage of the Service to better understand how Users use the Service.
In the event that Impress.ly or any part of its business is transferred to a third party, or if Impress.ly merges
with a third party, or undergoes a reorganization, your Personal Data may be disclosed and/or transferred
to that third party without your consent. Such third party will have to right to continue to use your Personal
Data and other information that you provided to Impress.ly in accordance with this Privacy and Cookie
Statement.
Impress.ly may disclose your Personal Data where it believes, in good faith, that it is necessary to comply
with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, criminal or civil subpoena, or other legal process or request
by law enforcement authorities or to exercise its legal rights or defend itself against legal claims.
4​.​ ​Where are the Personal Data processed?
The Service is provided by using hosting services of Amazon / Microsoft in the United States of
America. Amazon / Microsoft state that it adheres to the Safe Harbor principles and is certified with the
Safe Harbor program of the U.S. Department of Commerce. By using the Service, you agree to this transfer
and processing of your Personal Data outside of the EEA. We refer to the statements of Amazon / Microsoft
regarding this subject.
5.​ ​What security measures are in place to protect Personal Data?
The security of your data and that of other Users is very important to Impress.ly. We have implemented
technical and organizational measures to protect your Personal Data against loss and unlawful processing,
including without limitation the following measures: protection of our servers by firewalls, SSL connections
and encryption of sensitive data.

6.​ ​Cookies
Impress.ly uses cookies on the Websites. Impress.ly may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to
better understand how you interact with the Website, to monitor aggregate usage by our Users and web
traffic routing on the Website, and to improve the Website and the Service. A session cookie enables
certain features of the Website and the Service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect
from or leave the Website. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by
your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies help our Websites to recall specific
information on subsequent visits. The persistent cookies we use may for example remember your country
and language preferences, both based on you IP address. Persistent cookies can be removed by following
your web browser help file directions.
Impress.ly also uses third party tracking cookies, including but not limited to, Google Analytics, Google
AdWords Diversion, Google Dynamic Remarketing, and DoubleClick. Impress.ly uses these service to obtain
information about how visitors use the Website. Google may transfer this information to third parties if
required by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. We have no
influence over the processing of Personal Data by Google. The information is transmitted to and stored by
Google on servers in the United States. Google states that it adheres to the Safe Harbor principles and is
certified with the Safe Harbor program of the U.S. Department of Commerce. Please read the privacy
statement of G  ​ oogle​ (which may change periodically) which describes what they do with your personal
data via the cookies.
Additionally, our subdomain my.Impress.ly makes use of cookies provided by Visual Website ​Optimizer​,
NewRelic​ and ​Zopim​. For more information about how your personal data will be processed, please click on
the aforementioned names and you will be redirected to their privacy policies.
You may refuse to accept cookies, although this may restrict the functionality of the Website.
7.​ ​Third Party Apps and Products
Our Service may contain services and products offered by third parties, and/or hyperlinks to the websites
or services of partners, advertisers and other third parties.
Impress.ly has no control or influence over the content, websites or services of these third parties. Different
privacy policies may apply to the use of third party websites and services. This Privacy and Cookie
Statement only relates to Personal Data which have been obtained by Impress.ly through your use of the
Service. Impress.ly does not accept any responsibility or liability for the content, practices or operation of
third party websites and/or services.
8.​ ​Viewing and changing Personal Data
You can always view, edit or delete the Personal Data in your Account.
If you want to know what Personal Data Impress.ly has stored about you, you can contact Impress.ly by
sending an email to support@Impress.ly.

After receipt of this overview, you may request that Impress.ly correct, supplement, delete or block
Personal Data that is factually incorrect, incomplete, in violation of applicable law or not required to
provide the Service.
If you wish to delete your entire Account you can do so by sending an email to support@Impress.ly.com.
After deleting your Account, Impress.ly may store your Personal Data and Account for a further period of
time for a number of reasons, including but not limited to back-up reasons, legal obligations concerning the
retention of accounting information and the prevention of malicious actions resulting from identity theft or
other offences or crimes such as fraud. Deleted Personal Data and Accounts are only accessible by
Impress.ly and cannot be accessed by any users of the Service. All retained Personal Data continues to be
subject to this Privacy and Cookie Statement.
9​.​ ​Changes to this Privacy and Cookie Statement
Impress.ly may update this Privacy and Cookie Statement at any time. Impress.ly will publish any updated
version of this Privacy and Cookie Statement on the Website. Impress.ly encourages you to check the
Website from time to time to be aware of any changes to this Privacy and Cookie Statement. You
acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Cookie Statement
periodically and familiarize yourself with any updates.
10.​ ​What to do if you have any questions or remarks
If you have any questions or remarks about Impress.ly’s Privacy and Cookie Statement, please contact
Impress.ly via the Website or by sending an email to support@Impress.ly.
